# KHAREEN FRANCIS PROVERBS

# Software Developer

646-953-4323 @ khareenp1@gmail.com ♥ Troutman, NC

#### SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in developing web applications. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working primarily in small teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Python Coding Instructor

03/2023 - Present

Remote Classover

- Teach and lead coding classes online
- Inspire creativity and encourage curiosity in students
- Create safe, comfortable, and fun classroom environments
- Work with students to develop their own individual learning paths
- Ensure each student reaches their maximum potential
- Help students resolve any minor technical difficulties experienced during class

## **Entry Level Software Engineer**

01/2023 - 02/2023

Revature Remote

- Collaborate with other programmers to design and implement features
- Quickly produce well-organized, optimized, and documented source code
- Debug existing source code and polish feature sets
- Work independently when required
- Continuously learn and improve skills
- Attention to detail is essential and all tasks must be carried out to the highest standard

## Junior Software Engineer

07/2019 - 08/2022

## Taylor'D Technologies

**Barbados** 

- Researched, investigated, and fixed a wide range of bugs; documented and tested new software applications
- Used project management tools to track project performance
- https://bdsfinance.gov.bb/
- https://apps.apple.com/us/app/gls-barbados/id1454700769

#### 01/2022 - 06/2022 Intern Developer

# **Yick Solutions Inc**

Remote

- Designed and developed mobile applications and websites
- Debugged and tested code
- Collaborated with senior leaders and team members
- https://docs.modv.io/docs/

#### Technical Support Tier 2 Level 1

01/2022 - 03/2022

## **SONIFI Solutions**

Remote

• Which of your achievements match the job you're applying to?

#### **EDUCATION**

Programming in GO

06/2022 - 08/2022

Wiley Edge Training Program

Remote

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineer (Upper Second Class Honors)

2017 - 2022

The University of The West Indies

Cavehill, Barbados



#### **SKILLS**

#### **Tools**

HTML · Javascript · React · CSS ·

TailwindCSS · Postgresql · NodeJS ·

Python · Github · GitLab · Trello ·

MS Suite

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**



#### Deans List

Dean's list award in recognition of high scholastic achievement for academic year 2021-2022

#### **LANGUAGES**

Chinese(Mandarin) Beginner

. . . . .

#### FIND ME ONLINE



# Portfolio

https://khareenfp.netlify.app/

#### in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kharee n-francis-proverbs-57bb948a/

## GitHub

https://github.com/khareenp